let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which of the following comment is correct when a macro definition includes arguments?",
    answer: " The opening parenthesis should immediately follow the macro name",
    options: [
      "The opening parenthesis should immediately follow the macro name",
      "There should be at least one blank between the macro name and the opening parenthesis",
      "There should be only one blank between the macro name and the opening parenthesis",
      "All the above comments are correct",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: " What is a lint?",
    answer: "Analyzing tool",
    options: [
      "C compiler",
      "Interactive debugger",
      "Analyzing tool",
      "C interpreter",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Why is a macro used in place of a function?",
    answer: "It reduces code size.",
    options: [
      "It reduces execution time",
      "It reduces code size",
      "It increases execution time",
      "It increases code size",
    ]
  },
    {
      numb: 4,
    question: "In the C language, the constant is defined?",
    answer: "​Anywhere, but starting on a new line",
    options: [
      "Before main",
      "​​​After main",
      "Anywhere, but starting on a new line​​",
      "None of the these",
    ]
  },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "A pointer is a memory address. Suppose the pointer variable has p address 1000, and that p is declared to have type int*, and an int is 4 bytes long. What address is represented by expression p + 2?",
      answer: "1008",
      options: [
        "1002",
        "1004",
        "1006",
        "1008",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What feature makes C++ so powerful?",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "Easy implementation",
      "Reusing the old code",
      "Easy memory management",
      "All of the above",
  ]
},
{
  numb: 7,
  question: "Which of the following will copy the null-terminated string that is in array src into array dest?",
  answer: "strcpy(dest, src);",
  options: [
    "dest = src;",
    "dest == src;",
    "strcpy(dest, src);",
    "strcpy(src, dest);",
]
},
{
  numb: 8,
  question: "Each instance of a class has a different set of?",
  answer: "Attribute values",
  options: [
    "Class interfaces",
    "Methods",
    "Return types",
    "Attribute values",
]
},
{
  numb: 9,
  question: "How many instances of a class can be declared?",
  answer: "As per required",
  options: [
    "1",
    "10",
    "As per required",
    "None of these",
]
},
{
  numb: 10,
  question: " Which of the following SLT template class is a container adaptor class?",
  answer: "Stack",
  options: [ 
    "Stack ",
    "List",
    "Deque",
    "Vector",
]
},

];